smartfindsdirectory.com 2008-12-16

# | Smartfinds Article Directory | Article Submission | Article Marketing | Article Content

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

SmartFinds Internet Marketing respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data. We realize that the Internet raises questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment to safeguarding privacy to our Internet activities.

### Personal Information

SmartFinds Internet Marketing does not share, disclose or sell any personally information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on SmartFinds Internet Marketing web site with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non-SmartFinds Internet Marketing purposes. In the future, should SmartFinds Internet Marketing decide to share such data with third parties for marketing, it will provide notification and the opportunity for its users to indicate whether they would prefer that the Company not provide such information about them to third parties. Because this information is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. SmartFinds Internet Marketing also does not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from, children under the age of 13 on this web site.

### How We Use Information

SmartFinds Internet Marketing uses the personally information we collect and you provided to us principally to provide you with the service(s) you have ordered and to let you know about other offerings which may be of interest to you. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services.

SmartFinds Internet Marketing will provide personal information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with SmartFinds Internet Marketing property or services, or with our customers' or others' use of them.

### How We Collect Information

SmartFinds Internet Marketing collects information online by asking you for it, for example, when you order a service, apply for a job, or respond to a survey, sweepstakes or other promotion. A customer’s name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are the most important pieces of information, but we might request other information, based on, for example, the service(s) being ordered or promoted.

### Security

We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of SmartFinds Internet Marketing web sites and online services, you will need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information.

### Your Access to Information

You may review or update the available personal information that we received from you by contacting Customer Service through our e-mail address, [contact@smartfindsmarketing.com](mailto:contact@smartfindsmarketing.com). Please note that in order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

For questions regarding this policy, contact by email: [contact@smartfindsmarketing.com](mailto:contact@smartfindsmarketing.com) or by phone toll-free at (866) 501-5758.
